You caught the wrong person.
This isn't right!
What isn't right, Mom?
Evil is just lurking around,
isn't it?
Wait, I know this guy,
and Brother Tomas knows him too.
Good thing that crook
didn't finish you off.
He's ruthless, right?
We have no choice.
You'll be the one caught.
- You'll be Berdugo.
- What?
Surrender now, Berdugo!
You have nowhere to go!
That's what you think.
Even when I was right
in front of you,
you still couldn't do anything.
I'm sorry, Liza.
I will miss you.
Nice to meet the daughter
of the bravest man I know.
I think I've heard
that voice before.
I just can't remember where.
Everything is not what it seems.
Don't stop until
you get to the truth.
No, this is not Berdugo.
[OBB]
Oppa, what now?
I missed you!
This?
Chips.
Are you okay?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why? Aren't you happy to see us?
No, it's not that.
We have a problem.
What is it?
This...
That's Berdugo.
He, has a problem, not us.
He'll be jailed.
The problem is...
this is not Berdugo.
They got the wrong guy.
Are you sure?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, one hundred percent,
because I have seen him before.
Stop this nonsense!
Is this how you are
when I'm not here?
Their tempers just flared up.
I promise this is the first
and last time
that this will happen.
I hope so.
Because if not, I'll fix it,
and I promise you...
you won't like it.
I don't know his real name.
But I got a good look
at his face.
I can identify him.
If only I can see him again.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
And of course,
we would like to recognize
the person responsible
for the rescue of my husband
and the capture
of the notorious Berdugo,
Major Miguel Delgado.
- [APPLAUDING]
- [CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPPING]
On behalf of our Hope Circle
Foundation,
please accept
this People's Medal of Honor.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
You have no idea the impact this
has on me, Major Delgado.
Because of you,
we no longer fear Berdugo.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, Major? Is there...
a problem?
You know, Sir, I feel...
Even if we caught Berdugo,
his viciousness is still around.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Look at this report.
It looks like the other news
outlet has the same context...
about Berdugo.
Then let's change our approach!
That's why people watch us,
because we have our own take
on things.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, I know.
No one's interviewed...
Berdugo yet.
What if we get
an exclusive interview?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
No, no, no, we can't do that.
We'd just glorify the criminal.
What if we interview
the victim instead?
Mr. Tomas?
Oh...
didn't your brotherinlaw
work with Berdugo?
That's why he was chosen
as the victim.
Dude, that's great!
- Right? Right?
- Yes, I like that.
And the title's going
to be good, it could be...
"From Friend to Foe: Berdugo
in the Eyes of the Victim."
- Right? Old-school!
- Nice, nice.
So old-school! Right, Boss Idol?
That's right, Boss.
[PHONE RINGING]
Someone's calling me.
Hello?
Hello, Andrew?
You need to come
to the hospital now!
Why? Is there a problem?
Oppa said something.
Jin Ho said the real Berdugo
hasn't been caught yet.
What? Is this a joke?
No, the police got the wrong
Bersugo.
Okay, fine, I'll go there.
Take care.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
- Joey.
- Andrew.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is it true, what you said?
The police caught
a fake Berdugo?
Yes.
I know the real Berdugo.
He is probably planning
his escape now.
We need to stop him.
Berdugo is very sly.
And manipulative.
Matias just claimed
he was Berdugo
because he was ordered
to say so.
We were fooled
by the real Berdugo.
What are we going to do now?
Joey, did you tell your dad?
We're just waiting
for the cartographer
from the precinct.
If only I can get out of here.
I will look for Berdugo myself.
He still needs to pay
for Liza's death.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you again.
Because of what you did...
my men had a morale booster.
It is our pleasure.
So, Chief?
We'll go ahead.
- Thank you.
Ah, Major Delgado,
you have a new case already?
No, Sir.
It's still the old case.
Sorry, I just have something to
attend to.
Thank you, Mr. Limjoco.
Is the cartographer on the way?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Drink some water first.
Oppa, calm down.
Thank you.
The police are already on alert.
I'm sure Berdugo will be found.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
He won't get away.
We also bought
your snacks for later.
We'll surely take time
searching for Berdugo.
For now, think of details
you can share
to help us find him faster.
You're right, Joey.
I'll call my brother, Tomas.
I'm sure he knows
if Matias has associates.
Maybe one of those is Berdugo.
I'll just call him.
Mr. Limjoco also gave
a message to the police.
That's him!
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Our policemen are our real
heroes.
They give us.
That's him.
That is the real Berdugo!
Wait, are you sure, Oppa?
That's Andrew's family.
That's his brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
Your family...
he's a criminal?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, did you say food
business, Tomas?
- Yes.
- But you told me before,
your business was textiles.
Oh, right, textiles.
That was another client
with a food business.
My bad.
Everything is not what it seems
to be.
Don't stop until
you get to the truth.
Keep it to yourself.
Don't even tell your sister.
Next to them,
these criminal syndicates
are just small-fry.
That's why his voice
sounded familiar.
Whose?
You're in such a rush.
Why?
Are those people chasing you?
They're just small-fry
competition.
I've heard Sir Tomas's
voice before!
And what he said in his speech,
it's the same thing I heard him
say to Valmora
when Delilah and Berdugo
faced off.
I'm sure he's Berdugo.
Okay, we don't have time.
Let's tell the guards.
No.
Let me check on this first.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Check what?
I saw him.
And Joey heard him.
For what?
Are you going to warn
your family?
My family has nothing
to do with this.
And what you're saying,
those are just rumors.
We need solid evidence
if we don't want Berdugo
to escape.
The teddy bear...
In Ma'am Rebecca's room,
there's a teddy bear.
And it has a spy camera.
I'm sure it recorded
what really happened.
Did Ma'am Rebecca tell you that?
That you shouldn't
trust Sir Tomas?
I don't know,
she kept warning me.
The spy cam.
What spy cam?
When Ma'am Rebecca had a
heart attack,
she warned Mom about Sir Tomas.
Mom thinks it was
captured by the camera inside
the teddy bear.
Uncle Andrew, we need your help.
Okay, what is this?
You got this from
the teddy bear?
Yes, Kisses found it.
Let's see if it works.
Hopefully, it works.
I know where that is.
I'll go there.
- I'll find it.
- All right.
Wait.
Are we letting him go?
Yes, for evidence.
But he's right, Andrew,
you can't stay long.
If you're not back in 3 hours,
I'll tell Dad.
Thank you.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUN FIRING]
- [TOMAS GROANS]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Brother, is that blood?
There was a...
a branch on the driveway.
I wasn't looking.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want you to keep
an eye on Delgado.
All the movements of him
and his men.
Copy, Berdugo.
I'll watch them.
What if I just have
that Korean obliterated?
He's the only thorn
in my throat,
but he's heavily guarded now.
Too risky.
We'll wait for the right timing.
It's your call, Berdugo.
I'm ready anytime.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLICKS]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYS CLICKING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLICKING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BUZZING]
There's a group moving towards
the parking area.
It could be Berdugo.
Intercept!
- [GUN FIRING]
- [TOMAS GROANS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[♪STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING♪]
What are you saying?
Matias, he's not Berdugo?
Yes.
You have the wrong person.
If he's not Berdugo,
then who is?
I'm not joking with you.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, Andrew...
I was trying to call you.
Ah, I didn't know
that you were coming.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yvette, have you noticed
anything unusual
about Tomas lately?
What do you mean?
Something unusual,
something off?
Well...
earlier, at the precinct
and lately, he's been tense.
Ah...
and the other day,
he raised his voice at me.
That's not like him.
And then he's very impatient
and distracted.
Turns out he's stressed
because of this whole Matias
situation and the business.
But you know, I mean...
He's been dragged
into something illegal.
I mean, you know,
anyone would be shaken.
Why are you asking?
Andrew?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I didn't expect to see you here.
I came here to check on you,
Tomas.
Of course,
after what happened...
after Berdugo was caught, right?
That's very thoughtful of you,
brother-in-law,
but I'm fine.
In fact, it's you
I want to check on.
You and your friends,
you must all feel
very relieved...
Now that Berdugo
has been caught, right?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, I haven't seen them yet.
Since Matias was caught,
there hasn't been any reason
for me to meet them, Tomas.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm focused on work, on...
Tirada,
family.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Like now, I will...
just say good night to my nieces
and nephews.
- Yvette.
- Okay.
Hon, I'll just have them
prepare dinner, okay?
Okay.
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is there something
you're not telling me?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, let's just wait for Andrew.
What does Andrew have
to do with this?
He's just looking for something,
Uncle.
He's getting evidence.
What evidence?
You know we are just wasting
time here!
Yes, that is what I am saying.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, let's trust Andrew.
He's already done a lot for us.
This is the only thing he's
asking for, just a little time.
And he's on his way.
[CLOCK TICKING]
I don't understand you...
but I will do as you ask.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, Uncle Andrew.
Ah, Harris.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you still doing your
homework?
Ah, I'm almost done, Uncle.
So I can play the new video game
I want to play.
Do you want to join?
Next time.
Oh, by the way,
the reason I came here is
because I have a question.
Do you still remember
the teddy bear
you would always show me?
Is it still here?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
["NEVER SAY DIE" INSTRUMENTAL
PLAYING]
We're going to the rest house
to visit Mommy.
I'll go with you guys.
Major, this is Andrew.
Brother Tomas went with them.
Andrew, you go in first.
Bring your car.
Secure your family.
[GUN FIRING]
Dad...